KARLTUN MORENO

Full Stack Web Developer - Digital Media Specialist

karltunmoreno@gmail.com 818-317-4178

A professional web developer and effective communicator who is able to lead brand web production and web design. A thriving content media specialist that handles pre-production, production, and post-production under tight schedules. Fluent in English and Spanish. Also, a full stack developer; front & back end applications development manager. I am a passionate team player.

Portfolio @ https://github.com/karltunmoreno

TECHNICAL EXPERIENCE

Lightroom, In Design, Illustrator, Adobe Premiere, EP Movie Magic Budgeting and Scheduling, Red Camera, HDR, Bracket photos and Canon DSLR HD video cameras, RED cameras, ARRI cameras, DJI Mavic Pro Drone 2K, 4K 1080p, capabilities. Web design development/ Word press, Wix, Moonfruit. Intuit, HTML formats for I-Pads & cell phones. Mac OS & IOS, Android (Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint Final Draft, Final Cut Pro X, Photoshop, Adobe. Google Search Console, Sitemaps, GIT, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, JSON, API, AJAX, Node.js, MySQL, Mongo DB, MERN Stack, JQuery, Heroku, PWA's (Progressive Web Applications).

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer - *OuterBoundsPictures.com*

Web Developer - Karltunmoreno360.com

Instructor of entertainment design, gaming & code. FIT KIDS OF AMERICA June 2021 Producer for Commercials in social media include DORITOS, REAL ESTATE LISTING CONTENT VIDEOS (numerous) BLUE CAT FOOD, GUCCI FRAGRANCES,

NEW BALANCE, ARTIST TOUCH NEW YORK.

Director/Editor/ Producer "SHE," "GUNFIGHTERS" (short film)

Director/ Writer/ Editor/Producer "LADRON," "AWAKENING ATLANTIS"

Published Photographer on ELLE MAGAZINE, NAIL PRO MAGAZINE,

ABC NEWS, BEAUTY NEWS NYC MAGAZINE.

COTY - Associate Coordinator

Los Angeles, CA. Administration & Special Events. Scheduling, Logistics & Collateral Management. 08/2012 to 12 /2020

CLARINS - Brand Ambassador

Los Angeles, CA. Marketing & Merchandising. Scheduling, Public Relations & Special Events Planner. 06/2010 to 05/2012

PROCTOR & GAMBLE - Brand Specialist

Los Angeles, CA. Vendor/Client Relationships, Stocking, Storage, Sales, Counter Team Relationships, Public Relations, Collateral Management 10/2006 to 05/2010

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development & Coding Certificate

University of Miami - Miami, Florida.

Bachelor in Behavioral Science

California State University Northridge - Los Angeles, California.

Associate of Arts & Communication Miami Dade College - Miami, Florida.

• PART 107 CERTIFIED UAS PILOT - FAA - U.S. Department of Transportation